{
    "id": "2c403bb8ab3947c1858f1942ffc30446",
    "title": "Adverbs Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She worked ………………………… and passed the exam.",
            "description": "Hard is the adverb for this meaning. Hardly is also an adverb. Its meaning is similar to that of scarcely. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d8a2afc19b6a4442b1669593799fd435"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………………….. sorry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6d6758973404a7c8546985f8c1f88d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………………..see a lion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely",
                "scarcely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "988cea3b0597484d8b1cda7ecc67d785"
        },
        {
            "question": "She narrated the incident in ……………………….",
            "description": "In detail means thoroughly or in depth.",
            "answers": [
                "detail",
                "details"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b61ee3ab52314aef8de2592654f8dc0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was ……………………………. interesting.",
            "description": "Too has a negative meaning. It shows negative extremes.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "892c2591caed434cb8d28823b41bdc1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He behaved ……………………………….",
            "description": "Cowardly is an adjective. We need an adverb to modify a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "coward",
                "cowardly",
                "like a coward",
                "in a cowardly manner"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "7aac5ad3d4dd4b31bbe87197a31a4c2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel …………………………….. about it.",
            "description": "Feel is a copular verb. It is modified by an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f4500e9d2ec4fc7a525cde2f826b8c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………………. injured in the accident.",
            "description": "Badly is an adverb modifying a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "badly",
                "bad"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29117b956c304461848485459ab15c57"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ………………………………. horror movies.",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to watch",
                "watching"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67410092bfb645088440c97179edbfe2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although the tortoise walked …………………………….. he could beat the hare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slow",
                "slowly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bd2b5b67abe4c94853dcaa6c1043e31"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lecture was ………………………………. boring.",
            "description": "Quite and rather show a higher degree. Fairly shows a ",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather",
                "fairly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccf4116638dc4ca1a1b670d7a873d232"
        },
        {
            "question": "Read the article …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20078e5b3fff497d952b3ff9151ce2bd"
        }
    ]
}